Guide to the Stewart O'Nan papers, 1987-2009.
O'Nan, Stewart papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Stewart O'Nan papers, 1987-2009.
6851
Stewart O'Nan 1961-
circa 62 cubic feet.
Correspondence, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records documenting the work of writer Stewart O'Nan including manuscripts, books, research files and correspondence with publishers and other writers.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records documenting the work of writer Stewart O'Nan including manuscripts, books, research files and correspondence with publishers and other writers. The collection includes his research, drafts, tape recordings, books, and correspondence during the writing process for his varied books as well as additional correspondence and material. Papers from the following books are included:
Gardner Book
Snow Angels- A book about death, divorce and love experienced by an adolescent boy in the winter of 1974.
The Names of the Dead- Larry Markham struggles to win his wife back after she left him, but in the process finds out a trained CIA assassin and Vietnam veteran has been stalking him and his family.
Dear Stephen King
The Speed Queen- Inmate Marjorie Standiford tells the story of her life and how she began dealing drugs and moved to robbery and mass murder as she waits for her execution.
The War Back Home / A World Away- The story of a family torn apart when their son goes missing in action in the Pacific.
A Good Day to Die / Cuba Libre- Written under the pen name James Coltrane, this novel documents and attempt to retake Cuba.
The Vietnam Reader- A compilation of fiction, nonfiction, drama, poetry, film and more from the American War in Vietnam.
A Prayer for the Dying- Set after the Civil War, this book follows the crumbling sanity of a man living through an epidemic that is gruesomely killing the residents in his town.
The Circus Fire- An account of the great Barnum and Bailey circus fire in Hartford, 1944.
Everyday People/Summer People- A documentation of the day-to-day life of residents in an African-American neighborhood in Pittsburgh.
Wish You Were Here- A family mourns the death of a one of its members at their summer cottage and experience pain, rivalries, new love and hope.
The Night Country- The story of three deceased teenagers who come back to the world of the living for one chilling mission.
Upstate / The Good Wife- A pregnant woman discovers that her husband committed a crime and will be incarcerated for the next 28 years and struggles to cope with reality.
Faithful- A chronicle of the 2004 Red Sox season.
Last Night at the Lobster- This book follows a Red Lobster manager who is dealing with his pregnant girlfriend, Christmas shopping, and his love for a waitress as he corrals his team to keep working.
Songs for the Missing- A woman in an Ohio community goes missing and the family tries to hold itself together.
Clara (Screenplay)- A documentation of the life of Clara Schumann.
SUBJECTS
Names:
O'Nan, Stewart,1961-; King, Stephen, 1947-; Boston Red Sox (Baseball team); Red Lobster Inns of America; Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey Combined Shows
Subjects:
Circus.; American literature, 20th century; American literature, 21st century; Baseball.; Missing persons; Prisons.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
The collection is organized into series by book with general items appearing at the end of the series list.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Gardner Book
Box 1
Subseries I a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries I b. Miscellaneous
Series II. End of Memory
Subseries II a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries II b. Research/Notes
Subseries II c. Correspondence
Subseries II d. Miscellaneous
Series III. Snow Angels
Subseries III a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries III b. Miscellaneous
Series IV. The Names of the Dead
Subseries IV a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries IV b. Research/Notes
Subseries IV c. Correspondence
Subseries IV d. Editorial Notes
Subseries IV e. Miscellaneous
Series V. Dear Stephen King
Subseries V a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries V b. Research/Notes
Subseries V c. Correspondence
Series VI. The Speed Queen
Subseries VI a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries VI b. Miscellaneous
Series VII. The War Back Home/A World Away
Subseries VII a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries VII b. Research/Notes
Subseries VII c. Miscellaneous
Series VIII. A Good Day to Die/Cuba Libre
Subseries VIII a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries VIII b. Research/Notes
Subseries VIII c. Correspondence
Subseries VIII d. Miscellaneous
Series IX. The Vietnam Reader
Subseries IX a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries IX b. Research/Notes
Subseries IX c. Correspondence
Subseries IX d. Miscellaneous
Series X. A Prayer for the Dying
Subseries X a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries X b. Research/Notes
Subseries X c. Correspondence
Subseries X d. Miscellaneous
Series XI. The Circus Fire
Subseries XI a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XI b. Research/Notes
Subseries XI c. Correspondence
Subseries XI d. Miscellaneous
Subseries XI e. Media
Series XII. Everyday People
Subseries XII a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XII b. Research/Notes
Subseries XII c. Miscellaneous
Series XIII. Summer People
Subseries XIII a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XIII b. Research/Notes
Subseries XIII c. Miscellaneous
Series XIV. Wish You Were Here
Subseries XIV a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XIV b. Research/Notes
Subseries XIV c. Correspondence
Series XV. The Night Country
Subseries XV a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XV b. Research/Notes
Subseries XV c. Miscellaneous
Subseries XV d. Correspondence
Series XVI. Upstate / The Good Wife
Subseries XVI a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XVI b. Research/Notes
Subseries XVI c. Miscellaneous
Subseries XVI d. Correspondence
Series XVII. Faithful
Subseries XVII a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XVII b. Research/Notes
Subseries XVII c. Miscellaneous
Subseries XVII d. Media
Series XVIII. Last Night at the Lobster
Subseries XVIII a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XVIII b. Research/Notes
Subseries XVIII c. Correspondence
Subseries XVIII d. Miscellaneous
Series XIX. Songs for the Missing / Since You've Been Gone / Somewhere over the Rainbow / About a Girl
Subseries XIX a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XIX b. Research/Notes
Subseries XIX c. Correspondence
Subseries XIX d. Miscellaneous
Series XX. Clara (Screenplay)
Subseries XX a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XX b. Research/Notes
Subseries XX c. Correspondence
Series XXI. Screenplays by O'Nan and Others
Subseries XXI a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XXI b. Research/Notes
Subseries XXI c. Miscellaneous
Series XXII. Miscellaneous/Works by Other Authors
Subseries XXII a. Manuscript Drafts
Subseries XXII b. Other
Subseries XXII c. Books on Writing
Series XXIII. General Correspondence
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Gardner Book
  - Subseries I a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Bound Draft MSS (Box 1)
    - Boxed Draft MSS x3 (Box 1)
  - Subseries I b. Miscellaneous
    - Poetry, 1992-1998 (Box 1)
    - "OK Anthology" (Box 1)
    - Anne Bialke (Box 1)
- Series II. End of Memory
  - Subseries II a. Manuscript Drafts
    - MSS Drafts, June 1991 (Box 2)
    - MSS Drafts, January 1991 (Box 2)
    - Bound MSS hand revised draft (Box 2)
    - About a Girl MSS Draft, August 1996 (Box 2)
    - About a Girl MSS Draft, January 1993 (Box 2)
    - End of Message MSS Draft, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Boxed MSS, April 1992 (Box 3)
    - Bound MSS Unrevised, August 1991 (Box 3)
    - Boxed MSS, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Loose MSS Hand Corrected, n.d. (Box 3)
    - About a Girl MSS Excerpts, 1991 (Box 3)
    - About a Girl Bound MSS, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Subseries II b. Research
    - Journal, March 1989-August 1990 (Box 2)
    - Revision Journal, May 1991-July 1991 (Box 2)
    - Notes, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Subseries II c. Correspondence
    - William Morris Agency, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Subseries II d. Miscellaneous
    - MFA Thesis, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Sylvia Plath (Box 2)
    - Hardbound Thesis, August 1991 (Box 3)
- Series III. Snow Angels
  - Subseries III a. Manuscript Drafts
    - MSS 1st Pass Page Proofs, May 1994 (Box 4)
    - MSS 2nd Pass Page Proofs, August 1994 (Box 4)
    - MSS Copyedits, April 1994 (Box 4)
    - MSS Confirmation Proofs, August 1994 (Box 4)
    - MS Draft and loose chapter outline with original last chapter, November 1992-January 1993 (Box 4)
    - MSS Edits Bruce Tracey, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Boxed MS with new last chapter, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Subseries III b. Miscellaneous
    - Jacket Design and Blurb, March 1994 (Box 4)
    - Reviews and publicity: magazines, correspondence (Box 51)
- Series IV. The Names of the Dead
  - Subseries IV a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Bound MS, February 1995 (Box 5)
    - Loose Proof sheets and corrections, June 1996 (Box 5)
    - Bound MS, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Bound MS 1st Pass Galleys, October 1996 (Box 5)
    - MS Proofread Galley, September 1996 (Box 5)
    - MS Edits, 1996 (Box 5)
    - MS Confirmation Proof, May 1996 (Box 5)
    - MS 1st Pass Page Proofs, September 1996 (Box 5)
    - MS Copyedits, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Bound MS, December 1994 (Box 6)
    - Bound MS with Paul Cody letter and editorial notes, January 1995 (Box 6)
    - 6 copies Boxed MS, February 21, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Subseries IV b. Research
    - Outline and working chapter notes, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Working Journal, November 1993-January 1995 (Box 6)
    - Reading Notes, October 1993 (Box 6)
    - Cornell Notebook- The Violent Bar it Anyway, The Names of the Dead, April 1993 (Box 6)
  - Subseries IV c. Correspondence
    - Letter from Stephen King's office, September 1996 (Box 5)
    - Notes- Tobias Wolff and Jane Hamilton, September 1995 (Box 6)
  - Subseries IV d. Editorial Notes
    - Editorial Notes Bruce Tracey, June 1995 (Box 6)
    - Notes Denis Johnson, September 1995 (Box 6)
  - Subseries IV e. Miscellaneous
    - Blurb Material, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Doubleday Catalogs, Fall 1995 (Box 6)
    - Design Pages, August 1995 (Box 6)
    - Catalog Copy, n.d. (Box 6)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 51)
- Series V. Dear Stephen King
  - Subseries V a. Manuscript Drafts
    - MS Corrections in Ink, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Boxed MS Artist's audition sketches, October 1995 (Box 7)
    - Bound MS Working Copy, July 1995- October 1995 (Box 7)
    - Bound MS work copy with corrections (Box 7)
    - Boxed MS, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Later Version (Box 7)
    - Boxed MS, April 1996 (Box 7)
    - Loose MS, n.d. (Box 7)
  - Subseries V b. Research
    - Virgin Airlines Magazine Excerpt, May 1996 (Box 7)
    - 2 paperbacks (Box 7)
    - MS A. Manette Ansay's reading notes, April 1995 (Box 7)
    - Question List, Spring 1995 (Box 7)
    - Loose Notes, Spring 1995 (Box 7)
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 7)
    - Notes (Box 7)
  - Subseries V c. Correspondence
    - Paul Cody Postcard, June 1995 (Box 7)
- Series VI. The Speed Queen
  - Subseries VI a. Manuscript Drafts
    - MS Design Pages, October 1996 (Box 9)
    - MS 2nd Pass Page Proofs, July 1996 (Box 9)
    - Bound MS from Doubleday, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Bound MS from Doubleday, June 1996 (Box 8)
    - MS Final Corrections, September 1996 (Box 8)
    - MS 2nd pass page proofs, August 1996 (Box 8)
    - MS Confirmation Proofs, n.d (Box 8)
    - Design Proofs, n.d. (Box 8)
    - MS 1st Pass Proofs (Box 8)
    - MS 2nd pass proofs (Box 8)
    - MS Foul Pages and Original MS (Box 8)
  - Subseries VI b. Miscellaneous
    - Publicity Material, February 1997 (Box 8)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 52)
- Series VII. The War Back Home/A World Away
  - Subseries VII a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Boxed MS, May 1996 (Box 9)
    - Bound MS Pencilled Corrections (Box 9)
    - Bound MS Sloppy Work Copy, May 1996 (Box 9)
    - Boxed MS Original, November 1992 (Box 9)
    - Bound MS Revisions for Submission, February 1997 (Box 9)
    - Bound MS, October 1992 (Box 9)
    - Bound MS, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Boxed MS, May 1996 (Box 10)
    - MS 1st Pass Page Proofs, November 1997 (Box 10)
    - MS Copyedits (Box 10)
    - MS Page Proofs, October 1998 (Box 10)
    - Boxed MS, June 1996 (Box 10)
    - 2 Boxed MS Originals, June 1996 (Box 10)
    - Boxed MS, February 1997 (Box 10)
  - Subseries VII b. Research/Notes
    - Revision Notes, October 1992 (Box 9)
    - Loose Notes, Maps, and Research (Box 9)
    - Loose Revision Notes (Box 9)
    - Notes and Magazines (Box 10)
    - The Naked and the Dead by Norman Mailer, 1948 (Box 10)
    - Identification of Aircraft for Army Air Forces Ground Observer Corps, 1942 (Box 10)
    - A History of the War in Maps, in Pictographs, in Words by Rudolf Modley, 1943 (Box 10)
    - Marine at War by Russell Davis, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Journal for End of Memory and The War Back Home, October 1992 (Box 9)
  - Subseries VII c. Miscellaneous
    - Spotter Playing Cards (Box 10)
    - Aircraft ID Manual (Box 10)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 51)
- Series VIII. A Good Day to Die/Cuba Libre
  - Subseries VIII a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Boxed MSS, June 1998 (Box 11)
    - Boxed MSS, June 1996 (Box 11)
    - Boxed MS Original and Copy, August 1996 (Box 11)
    - Bound MS (Box 11)
    - 2 Bound MS Obselete Dictation Version (Box 11)
    - Boxed MS one loose, one bound, February 1996 (Box 11)
    - MS Signature Sheets (Box 12)
    - MS First Pass Page Proofs (Box 12)
    - MS Page Designs (Box 12)
    - MS Copy Edits (Box 12)
    - MS First Pass Page Proofs, November 1998 (Box 11)
    - MS 2nd Pass Proofs, January 1999 (Box 12)
    - Boxed MS 1 loose original, 2 loose copies, 2 bound copies, one with notes by A. Manette Ansays, March 1996 (Box 12)
    - Bound MS (Box 12)
  - Subseries VIII b. Research/Notes
    - Cliff's Notes for Whom the Bell Tolls (Box 11)
    - Notebook Sewanee Workshops, Journal, July 1995-February 1996 (Box 11)
  - Subseries VIII c. Correspondence
    - Correspondence W.W. Norton, Fall 1998 (Box 11)
  - Subseries VIII d. Miscellaneous
    - Paperback Copy of For Whom the Bell Tolls with changes in ink (Box 11)
- Series IX. The Vietnam Reader
  - Subseries IX a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Drafts of Chapter Intros, August 1995-April 1997 (Box 13)
    - Bound MS, two-volume version (Box 14)
    - Boxed MS (Box 14)
  - Subseries IX b. Research/Notes
    - Notes, January 1998 (Box 13)
    - Bound Course Packet for EN 242 American Vietnam War Narratives, Fall 1995 (Box 13)
    - Bound Oral History Project EN 242, Fall 1995 (Box 13)
    - 2 Loose Oral Histories, Fall 1995 (Box 13)
    - Notebook with Class Notes, Fall 1995 (Box 13)
    - Notes and Essays on Vietnam Films, August 1995-April 1997 (Box 13)
    - Notes and Drafts of Essays, August 1995-April 1997 (Box 13)
  - Subseries IX c. Correspondence
    - Notes and Correspondence, Letter from Tim O'Brien, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Permissions and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
      Includes letters from many American Vietnam authors
  - Subseries IX d. Miscellaneous
    - The 13th Valley by John M. Del Vecchio, 1982 (Box 13)
    - In the Lake of the Woods by Tim O'Brien, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Born on the Fourth of July by Ron Kovic, paperback, 1976 (Box 13)
    - The Only War we Had by Michael Lee Lanning (Box 13)
    - A Rumor of War by Philip Caputo, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Fields of Fire by James Webb, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Chickenhawk by Robert Mason, 1983 (Box 13)
    - American Myth and the Legacy of Vietnam by John Hellman, 1986 (Box 13)
    - In the Field: The Language of the Vientam War by Linda Reinberg, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Carrying the Darkness ed. by WD Ehrhart, 1985 (Box 13)
    - The Basic Training of Pavlo Hummel by David Rabe (Box 13)
    - Nam: The Vietnam War in the Words of the Men and Women Who Fought There by Mark Baker, 1981 (Box 13)
    - 365 Days Ronald Glasser, paperback, 1980 (Box 13)
    - The Vietnam Wars: 1945-1990 by Marilyn B Young, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Photocopied Selections (Box 13)
    - Loose Drafts of Essays (Box 13)
    - Loose Bibliographies of Vietnam Writing (Box 13)
    - Boxed Photocopy Pages (Box 13)
    - In Country by Bobbie Ann Mason, 1985 (Box 61)
    - Bloods: An Oral History of the Vietnam War by Black Veterans by Wallace Terry, 1984 (Box 61)
    - The Green Berets by Robin Moore, 1965 (Box 61)
    - Born on the Fourth of July by Ron Kovic, 1976 (Box 61)
    - 365 Days by Ronald J Glasser, M.D., 1971 (Box 61)
    - Meditations in Green by Stephen Wright, 1983 (Box 61)
    - Everything We Had by Al Santoli, 1981 (Box 61)
    - One Very Hot Day by David Halberstam, 1967 (Box 61)
    - The Killing Zone: My Life in the Vietnam War by Frederick Downs, 1978 (Box 61)
    - Combat Zone: An Oral History of American Women in Vietnam by Kathryn Marshall, 1987 (Box 61)
    - The Vietnam War in American Stories, Songs, and Poems edited by H. Bruce Franklin, 1996 (Box 61)
    - The Green Berets by Robin Moore, hardcover, 1965 (Box 61)
    - A Rumor of War by Philip Caputo, 1977 (Box 61)
    - Demilitarized Zones: Veterans after Vietnam edited by W.D. Ehrhart and Jan Barry, 1976 (Box 61)
    - The Basic Training of Pavlo Hummel: Sticks and Bones by David Rabe, 1973 (Box 61)
    - Obscenities by Michael Casey, 1972 (Box 61)
    - The Vietnam Experience: Images of War by Julene Fischer, 1986 (Box 61)
    - The Vietnam Experience: Combat Photography by Nick Mills, 1983 (Box 61)
- Series X. A Prayer for the Dying
  - Subseries X a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Bound MS Chapter Outline and Summary Notes, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Bound MS, 1997 (Box 14)
    - 2 Bound MS, 1997 (Box 15)
    - MS, 1997 (Box 15)
    - 2 MS Copyedits (Box 15)
    - MS Page Proofs, October 1998 (Box 15)
    - MS Design Pages, October 1998 (Box 15)
  - Subseries X b. Research/Notes
    - Notes (Box 14)
    - Journal, February 1996-December 1996 (Box 14)
    - Notes, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Subseries X c. Correspondence
    - Bound MS blurb letters from Robert O'Connor and A. Manette Ansay, 1997-1998 (Box 15)
  - Subseries X d. Miscellaneous
    - The Farm and Household Cyclopaedia, 1885 (Box 15)
    - Du Bay: Son-in-law of Oshkosh by Merton E. Krug, 1946 (Box 15)
    - Fire at Peshtigo by Robert W. Wells, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Snake Bite: Lives and Legends of Central Pennsylvania by James York Glimm, 1991 (Box 15)
    - Lost American Fiction: Weeds by Edith Summers Kelley, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Main-travelled Roads by Hamlin Garland, 1962 (Box 15)
    - American Woman's Home by Catherine E. Beecher and Harriet Beecher Stowe, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Maps, first try at voice (Box 14)
    - Readings of A Prayer for the Dying by Paul Cody and A. Manette Ansay, February 1997 (Box 14)
    - Loose Drafts of Essays (Box 15)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 52)
- Series XI. The Circus Fire
  - Subseries XI a. Manuscript Drafts
    - Boxed MS draft, April 2000 (Box 17)
    - Boxed MS First Draft, November 1999 (Box 17)
    - Boxed Draft Pages (Box 17)
    - MS Drafts (Box 20)
    - Galley Proofs, December 1999 (Box 21)
    - MS Confirmation Pages and Galleys, April 2000 (Box 22)
    - MS Drafts (Box 23)
    - Bound MS 3 Copies (Box 25)
    - Bound MS Revision Copy (Clown Face Cover) with ink corrections (Box 25)
    - Boxed MS Original revised, July 1999 (Box 25)
    - Bound MS Revision Copy (smoke over flags cover) (Box 24)
    - MS with Bill Thomas's Edits (Box 25)
  - Subseries XI b. Research/Notes
    - Eyewitness Accounts (Box 18)
    - Coroner's Report (Box 18)
    - Interviews (Box 18)
    - Oral Histories (Box 18)
    - Personal Recollections (Box 19)
    - Coroner's Report (Box 24)
    - Notes and Research (Box 19)
    - Manchester Circus file oral history (Box 20)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Publications and Magazines (Box 19)
    - Notes and Research (Box 24)
    - Loose material (Box 25)
    - Magazines (Box 23)
    - Investigating the Fireground by Calvin C. Phillipps and David A. McFadden, 1996 (Box 23)
    - The Great Hartford Circus Fire by Henry Cohn and David Bollier, 1991 (Box 23)
    - Burns, Shock Wound Healing and Vascular Injuries by Med. Dept. US Army, 1943 (Box 23)
    - No Next of Kin by Doris Miles Disney, 1959 (Box 23)
    - Master of Illusion by Mary-Ann Tirone Smith, 1994 (Box 23)
    - Freak Show by Robert Bogdan, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Dead Men Do Tell tales by William R Maples and Michael Browning, 1994 (Box 23)
    - The Chances We Take by Richard Goldhurst, 1970 (Box 23)
    - A Matter of Degree: The Hartford Circus Fire and the Mystery of Little Miss 1565 by Don Massey and Rick Davey, 2001 (Box 23)
    - Old Circus Programs and Route Books (Box 26)
    - Circus Magazines (Box 26)
    - Notebooks with Journal and Research Notes, February 1998-February 1999 (Box 26)
  - Subseries XI c. Correspondence
    - Letters from Family (Box 18)
    - Correspondence (Box 18)
    - Photo Permissions (Box 26)
    - Correspondence (Box 26)
  - Subseries XI d. Miscellaneous
    - Original artwork of circus grounds (Box 16)
    - Photographs from before and after the fire (Box 16)
    - Photocopies (Box 26)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 52)
    - Media related papers (Box 27)
  - Subseries XI e. Media
    - Mike Martin's Center Ring Videos: Ringling/Barnum Vol. Four, V-5939 (Box 27)
    - Mike Martin's Center Ring Videos: Ringling/Barnum Vol. One, V-5947 (Box 27)
    - Mike Martin's Center Ring Videos: Ringling/Barnum Vol. Two, V-5948 (Box 27)
    - Mike Martin's Center Ring Videos: Ringling/Barnum Vol. Three, V-5949 (Box 27)
    - Disasters of the Century: When Laughter Turns to Tears, V-5940 (Box 27)
    - American Justice "The Firestarters", V-5941 (Box 27)
    - Towers Productions show, April 4, 2000; V-5942 (Box 27)
    - Saebos Productions "Circus Stupendous", V-5943 (Box 27)
    - Paul Shafer's Hartford Circus Fire Video, November 4, 1998; V-5944 (Box 27)
    - Hartford Circus Fire, V-5945 (Box 27)
    - Hartford Circus Fire material, V-5946 (Box 27)
    - Mike Martin's Center Ring Video: Hartford Fire Documentaries, V-5950 (Box 27)
    - The Circus Fire, 2000; V-5951 (Box 27)
    - Borders Books and Music "Stewart O'Nan", June 7, 2001; V-5952 (Box 27)
    - Hartford Circus Fire Programs, 1991; V-5953 (Box 27)
    - History Channel's Circus Fire Special, V-5954 (Box 27)
    - Unlabelled, V-5955 (Box 27)
    - Circus Fire Perfect, V-5956 (Box 27)
    - Wrath of God: Hellfire, V-5957 (Box 27)
    - The Day the Clowns Cried, 1969; V-5958 (Box 27)
    - Circus Fire Commemoration, July 6, 2000; V-5959 (Box 27)
    - Rice, Vieths, TR-9251 (Box 27)
    - Vieths, TR-9252 (Box 27)
    - Judith Lowe, TR-9253 (Box 27)
    - Judith Love, Henry Cohn, TR-9254 (Box 27)
    - Henry Cohn, Virginia Anderson, TR-9255 (Box 27)
    - James Looby, TR-9256 (Box 27)
    - Helfer, Pringle, Paul Shafer, TR-9257 (Box 27)
    - Paul Shafer, Nancy Norton, Donald Anderson, TR-9258 (Box 27)
    - Donald Anderson, Tom Goodrow, TR-9259 (Box 27)
    - Tom Goodrow, TR-9260 (Box 27)
    - Ed McDonough, Joan Kelly, Elliott Smith, TR-9261 (Box 27)
    - Elliott Smith, TR-9262 (Box 27)
    - Elliott Smith, Joan Thompson, Donald Cook, Charles Teale, TR-9263 (Box 27)
    - Lynne Tuohy, TR-9264 (Box 27)
    - Lynne Tuohy, TR-9265 (Box 27)
    - Carrie Wilson, Annals of Surgery, HTFD Hospital, Spencer Torrell, Dr. LA Chotkowski, TR-9266 (Box 27)
    - Dr. LA Chotkowski, Robt O'Brien, Laura Kulick, TR-9267 (Box 27)
    - Laura Kubick, Lois Sheehan, Herbert Schook, Joe Martinelli, TR-9268 (Box 27)
    - Joe Martinelli, William Cieri, Marilyn Young Tarasuk, TR-9269 (Box 27)
    - Katheryn Pearse, John Pearse, Marilyn Young Tarasuk, Harvey Ofshay, Rivy Beizer, TR-9270 (Box 27)
    - Rivy Beizer, John H., Marna Thoma, Bradford Dennler, M. Eisenbero, TR-9271 (Box 27)
    - Eugene Roy, Robt Drayton, James Counihan, Stanley Cohen, Ed Lukstas, TR-9272 (Box 27)
    - Looby, Denato, Roy, TR-9273 (Box 27)
    - John Pedro, Alvin Kotler, Wally Kelly, Lewis Miller, Bud Jacobs, TR-9274 (Box 27)
    - Sanford, Heiser, TR-9275 (Box 27)
    - Heiser, TR-9276 (Box 27)
    - Heiser, Joseph Ruggiero, Nancy Cannon, Tim K., TR-9277 (Box 27)
    - Tim K., William Reid, Lee Steinberg, Hoffinger, Ellen Shuman, TR-9278 (Box 27)